[Reports & data](https://www.loblaw.ca/en/esg-reports/)[2023 ESG Report

(Open in a new tab)](https://dis-prod.assetful.loblaw.ca/content/dam/loblaw-companies-limited/creative-assets/loblaw-ca/responsibility-/ESG%20Report_ENGLISH_final%20AODA.pdf)

Effective date

October 16, 2023

Loblaw Privacy Policy
=====================

Loblaw Privacy Policy

At Loblaw Companies Limited, we respect your privacy and take great care in protecting your personal information. As a leading Canadian retailer, with operations spanning across the retail, health, and financial industries, we have millions of customers interacting with us each week – in our stores and through our websites and mobile applications. Through these interactions, our customers entrust us with their personal information.

Canadians rely on us to safeguard this information and ensure its responsible collection and use. To do so, we have committed to the following principles:

1. We will be transparent about how we handle your personal information and our privacy practices
    
2. We will use your personal information to benefit you and enhance your customer experience
    
3. We will protect your personal information and handle it responsibly

We also want to be transparent about how you can help manage your privacy and information, so you can make informed decisions.

Here's our full privacy policy and associated product/service-specific notices which describe our privacy practices in more detail:

#### Loblaw Privacy Policy

How Loblaw manages and protects your personal information, and your privacy choices.

#### Loyalty

How we manage and protect your personal information if you are a PC Optimum member and/or PC Insiders subscriber.

#### Health and Wellness

How we manage and protect your personal information when you receive healthcare services or use our PC Health offerings.

#### Interest-Based Advertising and Media

How we use personal information to provide tailored advertisements, and your privacy choices.

#### PC Financial

How we manage and protect your personal information if you have a PC Bank product, such as a credit card.

#### PC Insurance

How we manage and protect your personal information if you purchase PC home or auto insurance.

How do I know if there are changes to the privacy policy?
---------------------------------------------------------

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. Any changes we make will become effective when we post a modified version of the policy on this webpage. If we make any material changes to the policy, we will post a notice on our websites. By continuing to participate in our programs, and/or use our services or purchase our products after the modified version of the policy has been posted, you are accepting the changes to the policy, subject to any additional requirements which may apply. If you do not agree to the changes in our policy, it is your responsibility to stop participating in our programs, and/or using our services or purchasing our products. It is your obligation to ensure that you read, understand, and agree to the latest version of the policy. The “Effective Date” at the top of the policy indicates when it was last updated.

Who do I contact with privacy questions?
----------------------------------------

We have appointed dedicated Privacy Officers for Loblaw and for PC Financial respectively who are responsible for overseeing our privacy program and ensuring compliance with applicable privacy laws and regulations. If you have any questions about how we handle your personal information, please contact the appropriate Privacy Office noted below. If you have a program, product, service, or are participating in a promotion, contest or event that is offered by us with a third party, the third party may hold your personal information. If you have any questions or concerns, we will direct you to the appropriate party so that you may make enquiries as to that party’s privacy policies and practices. For all privacy related questions (excluding financial services):

### Loblaw Corporate Office - Privacy Office:

**Attention:** Chief Privacy Officer, Loblaw **Email:** [loblawprivacy@loblaw.ca(Open in a new tab)](mailto:loblawprivacy@loblaw.ca) **Phone:** [1-855-416-1244(Open in a new tab)](tel:1-855-416-1244) **Address:** Loblaw Privacy Office, 1 President’s Choice Circle, Brampton, ON L6Y 5S5

For privacy questions related to our financial services:

### PC Financial Privacy Office:

**Attention:** Chief Privacy Officer, PC Financial **Email:** [privacy@pcfinancial.ca(Open in a new tab)](mailto:privacy@pcfinancial.ca) **President's Choice Financial Phone:** [1-866-639-0012(Open in a new tab)](tel:1-866-639-0012) **Address:** President’s Choice Financial, 600-500 Lakeshore Blvd. West Toronto, ON M5V 2V9

For privacy questions related to Lifemark Health Corp.:

### Privacy Officer – Lifemark Health Group:

**Email:** [privacyofficer@lifemark.ca(Open in a new tab)](mailto:privacyofficer@lifemark.ca)

**Phone:** [1-866-446-3080(Open in a new tab)](tel:1-866-446-3080)

**Address:** 243 Consumers Rd, 12th floor North York, Ontario M2J 4W8

Have questions?
---------------

Contact us

®/TM Trademarks of Loblaws Inc., used under license. © Loblaw Companies Ltd.

About

Careers

News

Investors

Responsibility

EN   [FR](https://www.loblaw.ca/fr/privacy-policy/)

EN   [FR](https://www.loblaw.ca/fr/privacy-policy/)
